Hello friends welcome to my channel guys
welcome to my channel so guys
today's video is on ICCI Lombard General Insurance guys let me tell you
that very good results have been
seen in it let's talk about the third quarter
see in the December quarter itself the
net profit of private sector insurance company IC Lord which is known as General Insurance has
increased by 22.4 to
431 crores see in the same period last year the
profit of the company was 353 crores
whereas if we talk about the
net premium income of the company in the same time period it was
4690 crores see this
is more than the market expectations and
in the December quarter of the current financial year the
net premium income of the company was
estimated to be 4376 crores guys now if I
talk about the
solvency ratio of the company related to this it is at 257
and this
is much higher than the minimum regulatory level of 150 so that the
total income of the insurance company in the December quarter was
53 crores  Whereas
in the same quarter of last year, if we look at this figure, it was at
4362 crores. Guys, see,
along with the December quarter results, the company has also announced an
interim dividend of ₹ per equity share.
On January 16, the company's share closed at 0.18 in the Bombay Stock Exchange.
As you can see now,
today the
stock has closed at 1370 with a decline of 0.20 per cent.
But in the morning time, a
very good rise is seen in it.
You can say that the way the results have
come, then
you can see a very positive wave in it tomorrow.
If we look at ICCI Lombard, some time back, it had received a demand notice of 5.66 crores for
underpayment of GST in Goods and Services Tax. And
in the information given to the stock market, the general insurance company had told
that it had received a demand notice of 5.66 crores from Bhopal CGST, that is, Central
CGST and Central Excise Duty Joint
Commissioner, that is, how much, you can say 5
crore 66  A notice of GST demand of 2264 crores has been
received, guys, let me tell you that a
fine of 56602 crores was also imposed on the company,
if the total demand including GST and penalty is seen, then the payment is of 6.22 crores, guys,
yes you can say that its
impact was seen today as
negative, but if we look at the results, then there is a
lot of positive move, that is, you can say
that last year it was 353, which has now increased to
431, a
growth of 22% has been seen, in its
results, there will be some impact in the net profit, guys, it will definitely be
created tomorrow,
rest of the guys, I will say this to you,
study yourself, check and invest
and if you are new to the channel, then please do
not forget to like and subscribe, goodbye, thank
you, we will meet in the next video